Now we go to Jane who is going to tell us about what's happening in town this weekend.
现在我们交给简，她会告诉我们这个周末城镇上将会发生什么。
Right,thanks Andrew,and now on to what's new, and do we really need yet another sports shop in Bradcaster?
好的，谢谢安德鲁，现在有什么新鲜事，我们在Bradcaster真的需要另一家体育用品商店吗？
Well,most of you probably know Sports World - the branch of a Danish sports goods company the opened a few years ago,
你们中的多数人可能知道丹麦体育用品公司的分店“体育天地”在几年前开业，
it's attracted a lot of custom,and so the company has now decided to open another branch in the area.
并吸引了大量的客人，所以这个公司现在决定在该地区开另一家分店。
It's going to be in the shopping centre to the west of Bradcaster,
它将在Bradcaster西部的运动中心开业，
so that will be good news for all of you who've found the original shop in the north of the town hard to get to.
对于那些觉得原先在城镇北面的商店太远的人来说是一个好消息。
I was invited to a special preview and i can promise you,this is the ultimate in sports retailing.
我应邀预先参观，我向你们保证这将是体育零售业的旗舰店。
The whole place has been given a new minimalist look with the company's signature colours of black and red.
公司标志性的颜色黑色和红色带给整个地方一种全新的极简主义外观。
the first three floors have a huge range of sports clothing as well as equipment, and on the top floor there's a cafe and a book and DVD section.
前三层有大量的体育服装和器材，顶层有咖啡、书店和光盘区域。
You'll find all the well-known names as well as some less well-know ones.
你会找到所有知名和一些鲜为人知的东西。
If they hanven't got exactly what you want in stock they promise to get it for you in ten days.
如果他们没有你要找的东西，他们保证会在10天内为你找到。
Unlike the other store,where it can take up to fourteen days.
不像另一家商店要等上14天。
They cover all the major sports,including football,tennis and swimming,
他们覆盖所有主要的运动，包括足球、网球、游泳，
but they particularly focus on running,and they claim to have the widest range of equipment in the country.
但是他们特别关注于跑步，他们声称是全国拥有器材最为广泛的一家公司。
As well as that,a whole section of the third floor is devoted to sports bags,
除此之外，整个三层致力于运动包的销售，
including the latest designs from the States - if you can't find what you want here,it doesn't exist!
包括来自美国的最新设计。如果你不能在这里找到想要的，那么它就不存在！